=Born Again=
=Episode 13=
Hold it steady, honey.
Remember how you cut my body back then?
Now I'll pay you back.
Every time I fell before you,
you always stayed far away.
Finish this dance with me.
Remember,
this dance is tailor-made for you.
Gu Xiaotang,
I've done everything you asked.
Can you let me go now?
You're wrong.
It's you who won't let yourself go.
Not me.
You...
What do you mean?
Lu Qingyuan, look carefully.
These are all evidence
of your tax evasion,
embezzlement,
and forging medical records
to frame Xiaotang.
You used me,
deceived me,
and took me for a fool.
I think Director Li
has gone to you, right?
No.
He didn't go on a business trip.
The last time he showed up was
when he came to you with a recording.
That recording reveals
you'd kill for wealth,
even commit matricide.
Your reputation will be utterly ruined.
I should have guessed
it was you who recorded it.
Yes, I recorded it.
But you said those ruthless words
yourself.
By now,
the police should have
searched your study.
(Lu Qingyuan,)
(the image you painstakingly built)
(and the dignity you treasured)
(have all been destroyed by yourself.)
This is your end.
You wretch!
It's over.
It's all over.
This time we can finally
break the loop, right?
Ye Shen, thank you.
Without you,
I'd still be trapped
in that desperate loop,
going through the humiliation
and betrayal again and again.
You are tough enough to break the loop.
I just happen to be here.
No, not at all.
To be honest,
you've been helping me
from start to finish.
But I haven't done anything for you.
Do you have any unfulfilled dreams,
or
any regrets?
Tell me, I'll help you.
I...
I have no regrets.
Yes, you do.
Tell me.
Otherwise, I'd feel bad.
My regret was in my high school days.
There were some things
that I didn't get to say
or get to do in time.
Thinking back now,
it's all too late.
High school?
Then what exactly was it?
Tell me.
It's fine, it's all in the past.
Xiaotang, tell me.
Is this
the perfect ending you want?
Perfect?
Maybe.
This ending
is the best ending
I can achieve at the moment.
But Ye Shen,
if I could go back
to my high school days,
I'd want to go back.
Back then, I had
a wicked stepfather.
(I deeply regret)
(that I didn't have enough strength
to protect my mom,)
(and I didn't firmly make her
leave that man.)
(If I had been tougher,)
(my mom wouldn't have
fallen ill from depression)
(and left me so early.)
(I also deeply regret)
(that I didn't take my mom's advice.)
(I was obsessed with becoming a star,)
(chasing my star dream.)
(Party B's Signature)
(I dropped out of school
and signed that contract.)
One mistake led to many,
and that's why I'm stuck
with these nightmares.
So, if I could go back
to my high school days,
I'd want to change all of this.
But Ye Shen, don't worry.
I'll definitely help you
make up for your regrets too.
Even though you don't tell me now,
I'll find out eventually.
Gu Xiaotang.
You ruined my son.
You ruined the Lu family.
You'll die a horrible death.
Is it my fault?
You deserve all of this.
Nonsense!
It's all your fault.
Since you ruined us,
then I will make you pay!
Mrs. Lu, calm down.
It's all over.
Die!
Ye Shen.
Are you okay?
Retribution. This is retribution.
Gu Xiaotang,
how does it feel to watch
someone important to you die?
Since you ruined me,
then I will make you suffer!
It's okay, Ye Shen.
This ending isn't perfect enough.
Let's do it all over again.
What are you doing?
Stay back.
Do you want to die with him?
You're insane!
(Ye Shen, we'll meet again soon.)
(Ye Shen, no matter how many loops
I have to go through,)
(we will definitely
get the perfect ending.)
I...
(Gu Xiaotang's High School Days)
I'm back?
I understand now.
Even if I survived the wedding,
eradicated the Lu family
and all those villains,
the cause and effect
were already settled long ago.
As long as villains exist,
those I care about and I
will never be safe.
The loop isn't about
winning on the wedding day,
but going back
to the start of all the tragedies.
Alright.
This time, I must win.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪